Good morning.
good morning
Welcome to today's pick up
I'm very nervous.
Well...
Seriously, the atmosphere is totally different from usual.
Hi!
I'm looking forward to it.
Please...
Noe-chan.
I'm Noe-chan.
I'm Kayase-no-Yuru, the fruit ripper.
Please.
I haven't seen you since Pokemon.
After that, I had an important thing happen online.
I got beat up.
I don't want to do this.
I thought we were newbies.
I thought we were, but Nori's just going through the motions.
I was fooled.
But...
You didn't even know about the tying outfit.
I had no idea.
I thought, "What's she talking about?
Fire is weak against water.
It's like rock-paper-scissors-paper.
It's like a rock-paper-scissors-scissors type of thing.
I knew that.
I don't know.
I mean, isn't that a path everyone goes down once when they're kids?
That's true.
But...
Oh...
I haven't been there at all.
Oh, I see.
But I never had any battles or anything like that either.
I was really just a kid.
I'll go on then.
Please.
Wow.
I'm so nervous.
But you know what?
You're shy, aren't you?
Shyness is one thing.
Top idol.
No, no, no. I'm not.
You're right.
Sparkling in the moment
Fultz Zipper
They call me
I've heard a little bit about you.
When we were in Pokemon together.
I was so happy, I asked him if he was okay with me.
I was so happy that he was looking at me.
I'm super happy that you're watching me, like I'm really okay.
When I saw you on TV, before your debut, or on a comedy show...
Comedy shows?
I've seen you on comedy shows. Like, "Why?
When was your debut?
April 2022.
So it's already been two years.
But not soon enough? When did you make your debut?
About that summer. The summer I lived in the water.
Super fast. What were you doing before that?
I was a student before that. High school.
I wasn't really doing anything.
I did some freelance modeling work.
But it was just for pocket money.
Oh, an agency right out of high school?
I was an idol for a while while attending high school.
I was going to an international school in April.
What's that?
International?
I'm sorry, I don't know anything about it.
It's an English class for studying abroad.
What?
It's the same thing.
But in my case, it's German.
I'm German international, so it's like I'm taking German classes all the time.
You speak German fluently?
Yes, but I grew up in Japan, so I'm not very good at German.
Among people who go there.
Are there people who were born and raised in Japan who go to your school?
It's kind of like you can come in from the middle of the school.
I've started to see that.
I'm starting to see something like that.
Like Japanese, pure Japanese.
That's great, those people too.
They're great, aren't they?
It's amazing. English is a mash.
I wonder why they decided to use German?
I wonder why they chose German.
Because my parents liked it.
Like, "I love Germany.
Then go learn some German.
I'll have her memorize it.
I'll have her learn it in high school.
That makes you happy?
When I was a senior in high school.
That's about the time we got together.
Who would have thought you'd become an idol?
It was like we were idols before we knew it.
Isn't that amazing? I became an idol when I realized I was an idol, and then I realized I was successful.
I always wanted to work in music.
I wanted to be a musician, and then I was posting pictures of Salomo at Easter.
I was posting pictures of myself as a clothing model.
So you found my account there.
And they approached me.
Like a scout?
Yeah, something like that.
That's great that they found you like that.
Did you have many followers then?
Not at all.
A few thousand.
A few thousand followers for a regular person is pretty impressive, isn't it?
No, not really.
Almost all of them are hair stylists.
Followers.
That's great. They found me.
Yes, he approached me.
I was only 17 or something at the time.
I thought I'd do what I could while I was young.
I thought, "I'm an idol. I'm young, so I'm still allowed to do it.
So I decided to give it a try.
My family was very supportive.
They were really against it at first.
I see.
They want you to go to college.
You're worried about that too?
But it turned out better than I expected.
He's very supportive now.
Do you have a brother?
I have a brother, four years older than me.
I like older brothers.
Are you an only child?
I have a brother.
You have a brother?
I always wanted to be an older brother.
I mean, I'm the eldest.
But you don't have one, I guess.
I wanted a younger sibling too.
It's something that bothers me.
Did you want to take care of them? Even though I was little.
I had it when I was little, but as I grew up...
When you're an adult, or in junior high or high school...
I had to go up there and be firm, I guess.
I couldn't do it after all. But yes, that's what happens.
That's what I'm going to do.
I'm the eldest son, I'm the younger brother.
After all, you're the good one!
I'm solid.
Oh, I see.
Not at all. There are more families like that than you think.
Well, you know, I'm a role model.
Usually.
A role model, no, that's not true. I'm sure your brother is great.
I admire you, Kyonchin.
I'm so comforted by you.
No, I'm not! Because you've been very active.
He talks about me a lot now, but when I was young...
I had to borrow money from my brother.
I didn't know that.
I'm sure of it...
If that's what it took for you to get where you are now, then good for you.
I've already paid him back.
Good, good, good.
That's great.
Do you drink?
I don't drink at all.
Oh, you don't drink?
I feel like I'm 20 now, but I'm not.
You're 21?
I'm 20 now.
You're 20 now?
The 30th?
It's the end of December... the 29th.
And you're 21?
And I'm 21.
How old are you?
I'm 30 and I'll be 31 in September.
I have no idea.
You're off by 10.
No way!
I thought you were saying you were 26 or something.
I'm so happy!
Yeah, I'm still a girl who does things the right way, but I'm still the one who makes them do it.
Some people say I'm young and nice, but knowing my age, I'm not so sure.
You're 30 too, right?
Who are you to tell me I'm not cute?
I'll tell you who it is... and that you're not cute... and that you're not cute... and that you're not cute... and that you're not cute... and that you're not cute.
I'm not sure if I'd be able to work for a company if I were in the general public, but since I can't do that, I'm on this side of the fence.
I don't want you to say something like that to me.
The youngest is 4 years old.
Yay!
I mean, it's not like we have friends who are 20 years old... or even normal people.
Do you consider me a friend?
I totally do.
Yay!
I mean, don't you want to play Pokemon online with someone you're not friends with?
Sure.
We've met a few times on the field, but we've never really talked much.
Yeah, we don't have a lot of time with everyone else around.
That's right.
I wondered if it would be okay, but now I'm sure of it.
I'm sure you're busy, so I'm totally flexible. Really? -I'm very flexible.
If we can meet up on a certain day, we can go out together.
I don't know what it is, but... you often go out with your idols. Really?
We often talk about Noel.
I'd like to get together with her. She told me about Pokémon.
I wanted to invite him today.
They say, "Why don't you call her?" They say, "She's busy.
But I think she's too busy, and she's a little too young.
They said it wouldn't be harassment if I called her.
I'm totally flattered. I've given it a lot of thought.
Is there anyone you get along with? Idols?
Any of them.
Someone you're close with? Even comedians?
But I'm friends with Mayarika because she's my official big brother and I work with her on the show.
We've become good friends, but we don't hang out in private.
But he's really nice to me.
I love the Tosa Brothers.
That's right. But the Tosa Brothers invited us to their event.
That's right. It's the first time.
I think we took pictures.
The Tosa Brothers are so nice to us.
They always give us flowers at our shows.
That's right. I always think they're so sweet.
They're the best!
Do comedians have official big brothers, too? No, they don't.
I thought it was just for idols. We do it on our own.
They take care of us whenever we need something, so they should be our official big brothers.
Miki's the one who discovered us.
I've taken the liberty of making Miki-san my official father. You've gone above and beyond.
That's amazing! That's so cool!
One time in the play system, Kiri-chan.
Mizuki Kirihara.
What did I call you?
I think we called her Kiri-chan together on Noburoku TV.
I see.
That course was very intense.
Around 20 years old.
We had a fight, and Suga-chan was really bullying her and harassing her, and we had a surprise to see how she would handle it.
But we also did one where Suga-chan said she wanted to quit.
I know we're all human and each of us has our own feelings.
He said some really nice things. I mean, how old is he?
You're a very mature person, aren't you?
But I think so, too, Shinoyuri-chan.
You're kidding?
Yes.
Thank you.
She's the kind of girl who wouldn't hurt anyone.
Wouldn't you hate it if someone did that to you?
I wouldn't like it, but I'd say it.
That kind of thing.
It's just something that comes out of my mouth.
But I understand.
I totally understand.
So, in my mind, I'm like, "Why is this guy doing this?
That's how I feel.
Sometimes I do.
He's a human being.
That's good. That's good.
What if he's someone who doesn't see people?
I'm totally, totally, totally human.
Very, very human.
Is there anyone you're happy to see?
Anyone who was happy to see me?
Uhhh...
Aah! But let's see...
Tamori.
That's right.
I was allowed to take out my insect hands just once.
I was...
That's when I met Tamori for the first time.
You seem to really love him. That's nice.
We often talk about him.
Senior comedians, like Samma...
Downtown... and we're like, "Yay, yay, yay" to meet him.
How do you meet Tamori? The only way is to appear on M STAR.
I'll put out a song? Something like that.
A song... yeah.
I'm sure Tamori would love to go.
On top of that, on TV, you only get to see him from the front.
On M-station, you sit behind him.
So you get to see the back of Tamori's head.
Wow, look at that!
The back of Tamori's head!
Look, what color is it?
What color?
That's something you'll have to wait and see.
I'd love to see it.
I'd love to go behind your back, wouldn't you?
I've seen you on TV, so I'm glad to see you.
I thought, "What?
I can't believe you're here reading this.
Manatee loves comedy, and so does Party-chan.
And she likes Party-chan, too. That's why she got the job.
I'm so jealous that I got this job today.
I wish I could stay longer.
I'm sure you'll be very happy to see me again.
There are more colors in a book, but they're all together like this.
They get along really well... it's amazing... but they're all adults to some extent...
I see. I'm the youngest at 20.
I see. There's no one in their teens.
Do you have a best friend?
The person I'm closest to...
But Matsumoto Karen?
Karen Matsumoto, the pink girl.
They're close in age.
We get along well.
Do you go out?
We go out for yakiniku.
It's not often that we get together.
But when we go on an excursion...
Just the two of us.
Sounds like a lot of fun!
Sounds fun.
But even if it's after work...
The next day is the best time to go on an excursion.
That's right.
If you're going out for fun...
Or go to a theme park.
Oh, you go to theme parks?
I love theme parks.
I saw it on your Instagram.
Really?
You know, the ones where they find all the good stuff...
Oh, really?
I told you.
That day...
I had to work till about midnight.
So I said, "Let's splurge.
I took a cab with the guy who went with me.
We took a cab and took a cab home.
Oh, man!
I was doing it!
So I'm kind of...
I'm so tired.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't worry, I'll give you a ride home.
What?
That's more extravagant.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I love to drive.
Is that why you're doing this project?
Yes, yes, yes. I like doing it.
And I like talking to people.
When I started YouTube.
I wanted to talk with people anyway.
If I'm going to do it somewhere...
I have a car and stuff.
I'm going to do it.
I'm really excited about this project that you can do.
It's so good, it's the only way to do it.
If I can keep my car, I'll end up with youtube... I don't like that, I hope it doesn't go away!
I hope it doesn't disappear!
I like to drive. I'm not in Japan now, but when I come back to Japan...
I hope you'll do your best!
He takes me to all kinds of places by car.
He says driving in Tokyo is scary.
You're used to it.
I'm used to it.
It's partly because I'm from Kanagawa.
I used to come here all the time.
I see.
By car?
I came by car because I don't like trains.
But I had a car when I was in my hometown.
I came to Tokyo when I was about 21.
Of course, I couldn't bring a car.
I sold my car and came here alone.
I turned 30 last year? This year?
This year? For my birthday.
The last time I bought a car, I was 20.
You bought it when you were 20?
You got your own tan plate?
That's amazing.
I'm turning 30.
I happen to have a parking spot at my house right now.
I wasn't using it.
I said, "Well, I'll just get one.
I bought it, but I've been going out a lot with my carcia and stuff.
I was moving late at night.
I see.
And there's no train.
Of course, I can't go out for a drink or anything, but...
I like to go to the spotcher.
You know, when we go to those things, we drive, right?
A car would be nice.
When I was used to it.
I could drive without any problem at all.
But...
So you've been an idol? Since high school.
Since my junior year of high school.
And even then you didn't have time to go get your license?
Yes, I did.
Your face changes a lot when you've been doing it since you were in high school, doesn't it?
It changes a lot.
That's right.
And at that time, I was working as a model for a long time, so I didn't have the opportunity to do my own makeup.
I see. So you had a makeup artist.
That's right. So, when I became an idol and went to Taiwan, I didn't have a make-up artist,
So, when I became an idol and went to Taiwan, I didn't have a make-up artist.
That is normal.
So I had to do my own makeup.
I had to put on eye shadow, eyeliner, blush, and so on.
I went out on stage with almost no makeup on.
That's right, you had someone else do it for you while you were learning.
That's right. I didn't know what I was doing, so I just did it like that.
I didn't apply eyelashes or mascara.
I don't apply mascara or eyelashes now, but in the beginning, I really didn't apply mascara.
In the beginning, I really didn't do anything.
But you know, my original face is so clear.
But you're lucky.
I'm so jealous. I'm not going to be like, "What the hell is he doing without makeup?
I'm so jealous. But it makes you look younger than you are.
No, I don't. Really?
I'm told I look very mature.
Really?
I'm only 156.
You're smaller than I thought when I saw your face.
But you look tall.
I'm really, really...
Blind eyes. When you make him lie down, he has blind babies' eyes.
You know...
He looks just like that one.
What, like Bryce?
I don't know.
I don't know what it's called.
I don't know what it's called, but it's one of those things.
I don't know if he drinks or not, but that's part of it.
I was wondering what it was like to be an underage girl.
I'm glad to see you're 20.
You can totally call me. Seriously?
I'd love to go. I'd love to go.
You're shy, right? I'm shy.
But I don't feel that way at all.
I find it easier to talk one-on-one.
I am. Oh, I see.
In a large group...
I'm kind of stuck in the corner.
How big is a group?
Uh, let's see...
Just five, I think.
Well, maybe four.
Four is still fine.
Let's have a Costco party at my place.
Costco? I've never been there.
Seriously? Shall we go?
Oh, I want to go!
We go to Costco all the time.
It's so exciting!
We're free. Let's go.
I want to go to Costco!
We'll go!
Sounds fun!
They sell these huge sea grapes!
Oh, that's great!
Are they fresh sea grapes?
Fresh.
They sell fresh sea grapes?
I buy snacks and stuff, but I'm really excited to see a big potato chip like this.
That's for sure.
I was like, "What?" and I could only eat this much.
Potatoes definitely make me sick to my stomach.
You know...
I've always had a weakness for fat.
I'm serious.
Already now
I'm probably more fatty than most 20-year-olds.
I can't even eat meat or grilled meat.
You're a belly eater?
I do eat meat.
But they come pretty fast.
Are you kidding me?
That's terrible.
Yes, it is.
My stomach isn't quite 20 years old.
It's not good.
What do you enjoy eating the most?
I don't know.
Tomatoes.
Tomatoes and porridge?
Rice porridge?
I love porridge.
I can't believe it.
You can't believe it?
Until recently, my favorite food was gummy bears and French fries.
Then it changed to tomatoes in the last year.
It's the same.
Until then, I didn't want to eat vegetables.
I see.
I did, but then I realized my body was in trouble.
I love tomatoes so much, I eat them all the time.
I eat tomatoes all the time.
If you're eating tomatoes when you're 20...
I'm serious.
When you're 30 or something...
I mean, really, grass.
You're not gonna eat nothing but leaves, are you?
What do you think?
But I've loved tomatoes since I was a little girl.
I ate a lot of cucumbers and carrots.
I'm a veggie kid.
I also liked green peppers.
Really?
I'm an adult.
But I didn't like bitter melon.
Aren't they the same? Bell peppers and bitter melon...
They're not the same. Really? The bitterness is different. Bitter melon makes the back of my mouth more bitter.
but bell peppers are different.
It's a little bitter. Really? Like green tea. Oh, I don't drink green tea. So I'll say it. I don't like bitter tea.
I really don't like bitter things. On the contrary, I recently came to be able to eat bitter melon.
But when I ate it recently, it was better than before.
It's better than before, but I still can't eat bell peppers.
I don't know what to say.
It's like grass? They're so green, you can't miss them?
I don't know.
I really didn't like it.
Oh, I see.
That purple guy has a bad stomach.
He's so girly!
He has a gyaru face.
Heh...
She has a gyaru face.
That's right.
She says "peepee" and that kind of thing.
I like her face.
Really?
She's really cute.
But he's cute.
He's super cute.
They're all cute.
They're all so cute.
It makes me nervous.
Don't worry, they're cute.
Everyone says it, even the girls I'm close to.
They're all so cute, I really don't know what to do.
What's there to worry about? You're pretty enough yourself.
What are you talking about? Are you stupid? I'm just saying...
But if everyone around you is cute...
It probably lowers their self-esteem.
I see.
That's what I thought.
I thought that girls in the entertainment industry
are sometimes lower than normal girls.
I think that a lot. Because they are by far the prettiest.
No, seriously, I ignored it.
I ignored it.
I think so much.
Everyone is cute. Happy is good, isn't it?
it's cute to say
Yay!
It's cute when you say it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
There was a time when I really couldn't have a conversation with anyone because they'd start singing.
I couldn't really have a conversation with them because they would start singing.
But I understand that too. It's like, "Oh! It's like you said it.
And when other people around me say it, I'm like, "Oh! It's really a normal conversation.
It's amazing how it gets into the subconscious.
It goes right into the human brain.
It's too amazing!
It's amazing! It's amazing!
That's right. It's all of it!
It's all in there!
So, this song was written by a guy named Sho Yamamoto.
It's really amazing!
It's a hit that was meant to be a hit.
The song and choreography are amazing!
Fruit Zipper is amazing!
Thank you for taking us!
I can't thank you enough.
You're right.
Laughs.
It's fun for the ears and the eyes.
It's fun.
Yes, it is.
It's almost time to go to breakfast.
You're early.
Not at all. Next time we're dressing privately.
What? I caught the Star Manor Day... and I caught the fish.
You'll be pleased.
We're here. Thank you Naganaga.
It's nice to meet you too.
I'll be back to play with you in private.
I look forward to it. Thank you very much.
Is this a video until we get off?
Yes, you don't have to get off.
No need to get off.
Bye-bye.
Thank you so much.
Yay.
Don't come to this place.